export const questions = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "What is the meaning of Water ?",
    options: ["Água", "Bread", "Salt", "Sea"],
    solution: "Água",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the meaning of Bread ?",
    options: ["Pão", "There", "Are", "So"],
    solution: "Pão",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What is the meaning of Think ?",
    options: ["Pensar", "Sink", "Dishwasher", "Can"],
    solution: "Pensar",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is the meaning of Space ?",
    options: ["Espaço", "Plane", "Ship", "Car"],
    solution: "Espaço",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is the meaning of Remind ?",
    options: ["Lembrar", "Mind", "Brain", "Annotate"],
    solution: "Lembrar",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What is the meaning of knife?",
    options: ["Faca", "Fork", " Spoon", "Toothpick"],
    solution: "Faca",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is the meaning of door?",
    options: ["Porta ", "Unshift ", " Always ", " Roof"],
    solution: "Porta",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What is the meaning of monster?",
    options: [" Monstro ", "Way ", " Castle ", " Palace"],
    solution: "Monstro",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the meaning of winter?",
    options: ["Inverno", "Summer", "Spring", "Autumn"],
    solution: "Inverno",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What is the meaning of tree?",
    options: ["Árvore", "Flower ", " Branch ", " Bush"],
    solution: "Árvore",
  },
];
